# JUAN GARCÍA

COMPUTER SCIENTIST

Born in Barcelona, 1994. I am passionate about science and technology, also interested in project management, business and communication. During recent years, I have taken part in numerous hackathons throughout Europe. I have also worked on projects of my own that you can check on GitHub or Devpost, linked on my website below. My specialisation is Artificial Intelligence.

#### EDUCATION

**BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE**POMPEU FABRA UNIVERSITY, BARCELONA | SEP 2013 - AUG 2017

MASTER'S DEGREE IN ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE
UNIVERSITY OF ABERDEEN, ABERDEEN | SEP 2017 - AUG 2018

## EXPERIENCE

#### **DEVOPS ENGINEER**

TRACKTIO | NOV 2015 - SEP 2016

- Full Stack software development in Node.js, Javascript, HTML and CSS
- Hardware development and deployment.
- Server management
- Database design and maintenance
- Big Data Back-End development for LORA
- 3D modeling for RTLS

#### HEAD OF THE DEVELOPMENT DEPARTMENT

GEOMAR | JUN 2017 - PRESENT

- Project Management
- Online Advertising and Marketing
- Full Stack software development in Node.js, Javascript, HTML and CSS
- Server Management

#### AWARDS

#### UK Datalab Award in Artificial Intelligence

Scholarship for Master's Degree in Artificial Intelligence

#### SKILLS

- Artificial Intelligence
- Advanced Algorithms
- Software Development
- Back-End and Front-End Development
- Database Design
- Algorithm Design
- Python
- Java (Including Web Services)
- Network Security
- CUDA
- System Testing

- Advanced Math and Physics
- Signal Processing
- Probabilistic Models
- Genetic Algorithms
- Distributed Systems Design
- C/C++
- Node.js
- HTML5, CSS3 and Javascript
- Android
- Project Management
- R
- Data Science

#### CONTACT

+34 672210152 ASTRAY53@GMAIL.COM JUANGMN.ME

### LANGUAGES

• English: IELTS Proficiency

Spanish: Native

• Catalan: Native

• Japanese: Beginner